[theme music playing]
[laughs]
[Lily] So you two are
working together now?
Is this a new form of torture?
[Helena] I didn't take your
resignation very well.
-Once you're in…
-[crowd screaming]
…the only way out is death.
[Julio] I'll be sending you an address.
Once you receive it, you have to
be there within 20 minutes.
Because if not,
your precious love will die.
[goon] Someone more powerful
wants to hire us.
We already made a deal, and I and
my men will start working for her now.
I'm sorry, Jaguar. It's just business.
Nothing personal.
[Helena] There's a gun hidden
somewhere in that warehouse.
You have to end each other's life
with a single bullet.
[Diego] Damian! We're on the same side!
[Damian] Say your prayers!
[Diego] If you kill Lily,
how will Camia ever love you?
[Emilia] That's it! Come on!
Yeah!
[Damian] I've lost Camia
lots of times before!
I won't let that happen again!
In the end, it's us who will survive!
[somber music playing]
[somber music continues playing]
[Jepoy] Hello?
Didn't you receive my messages?
Yeah, I really need backup!
Look, wait,
I can't pay you anything for now.
But hear me out.
I'll do anything you want.
It's not like that, but--
Hello?
[screams in anger]
[tense music playing]
Jaguar?
[exhales sharply]
How stubborn.
I already told you,
you won't get any help from us.
What are you doing here?
If I had someone else to turn to,
you wouldn't see me here.
-Now, where's your boss?
-[clicks tongue]
Let me guess.
You need Jaguar's help, don't you?
[goon] Why do you all
let Lily Cruz walk all over you?
You'll do anything just to save her.
How do you know why I came here?
Do you know something
I don't? Spit it out.
Madrigal…
We're the only ones you can go to now.
Unfortunately for you…
we just broke away from Jaguar.
[scoffs]
Then, I don't need you anymore.
Madrigal.
Why are you in a hurry?
Why don't we have a little chat first?
Didn't you hear what I said?
I said…
I don't need you anymore.
[grunts]
Hey!
-Back off!
-Hold him!
-Hold him down!
-Let go of me!
[grunts]
-Here you go.
-Take a break.
Thanks, Boss.
-I got this.
-Okay.
Go.
The boss said we should take a break.
-Really?
-I think he's up to something.
-Let's go.
-Nice.
Don't come near me.
Come on.
I just brought you food.
-You should eat.
-I don't want to.
I'm not hungry.
You might get weak.
Sorry about earlier.
The Governor told me…
to do whatever I wanted.
The truth is…
I don't like taking advantage
of helpless women.
I like them feisty.
[screaming] Stop it! Let go of me!
Stop!
So, you're telling me…
that your mother can fight too?
[Julio] Is that it?
Well, listen closely.
Right now…
my henchman's pulling down
his pants zipper.
Because he's going to rape your mother!
[Camia screams]
No! Stop it!
-[in low voice] You monster!
-So, even if Damian wins,
your mother…
is just going to be a shell of herself.
[Camia screaming] Let go of me!
[Julio] My henchman will make Camia relive
her worst nightmare…
[Camia sobbing]
…with one change
to what happened in the past.
You bastard!
-Bastard--
-This time, that worthless Raul
won't come to save your mother
to dig her out of her grave!
-You demon!
-Don't worry, don't worry!
It's going to happen.
Because I've got everything figured out.
And I want you to remember that.
[Julio] I want it ingrained in your mind.
Because I want you to feel…
every bit of pain.
I want you to witness it yourself!
Julio, you damn monster!
You're a monster!
When I get out of here,
I swear I'll kill you, you bastard!
Look at you.
What are you talking about?
[Julio laughs viciously]
It's show time!
[crying] You monster!
Mom…
Julio, you monster!
You bastard!
Mom!
[Lily sobbing]
Well…
It was nice…
talking with you,
Lily Cruz.
It was nice hearing your…
empty threats and your…
your silly promises.
[laughs viciously]
Come on!
Admit it.
You knew this was going to happen.
-You haven't won!
-What--
When I get out of here,
I swear I'm going to kill you!
And I'll start with your family!
What you're doing to me
and my family now?!
I'll give it back worse!
Blah, blah, blah!
What's wrong with you?
You know, we're no different
from each other.
We come from the same cut of cloth!
You act like you're so noble
when truth of the matter is,
you're nothing but just another egotistic,
power-hungry little witch
who wants to rule over this town.
And you don't mind you're going to do it
even at the expense of the ones you love!
You're filth!
You, of all people?!
Look in a mirror, Julio!
Are you seriously projecting
your screwed-up morals on me?!
Like we're the same?
You're trash! You senile old man!
That is why…
Demons always win!
[Lily] No!
Good always wins!
Mark my words, Julio Ardiente!
I swear on this spot…
where innocent blood was spilled…
including my father's, Nanny Carlotta's,
Miss Loring's, and Mr. Pandoy's.
I swear on all of them.
No more blood will be shed.
Not one innocent shall die again!
I will end you,
Julio Ardiente!
You and your family will perish!
But, before that,
you'll all beg for mercy!
Your souls themselves
will beg for my mercy!
[action music playing]
[screaming]
[timer beeping]
[Damian] Come on.
Put it on.
[Julio] Wow!
How nice.
Sit!
It's nice, your new collar.
[grunts]
[ragged breathing]
Maybe I should change your name
from Lily to…
Fifi?
[laughs viciously]
[in silly voice] A cute little dog! Fifi!
-And this…
-Damn you!
And this will make you shut up!
-[electric shocks]
-[Lily gasps]
[Julio] Surprise, surprise, surprise!
Learn to follow your master.
Damn you…
Sit. Stay. Roll over.
[laughs viciously]
I'll get back at you, you bastard.
My God.
She never gives up!
And I'll get back to you.
But, for now,
I think I will leave.
[Julio] It's hot here!
Bye, Lily Cruz!
Enjoy and watch the show!
A lot of other things will happen!
[Julio laughs viciously]
Goodbye!
[screams in anger]
-[screaming]
-[sobbing]
[Camia sobbing]
Is this what you really want?
You don't need to force me.
I'll give you what you want.
But since you brought food.
Can I eat first?
Sure.
Can you untie me?
My wrists hurt.
I can't.
I'll just feed you.
You might try to escape.
[retches]
[grunts]
Hi, Madrigal, my love.
[Natalie] I heard about what happened.
Do you need me to help you stand up?
I can do it myself.
[grunts]
Well, obviously, you can't help yourself
because someone has
black and blue eyes now.
Your face is purple.
Maybe, you need another person's help.
I don't know.
Maybe Nurse Natalie, perhaps?
Where am I?
-Let me help you.
-Where am I?
-Don't touch me.
-Stop being so difficult.
[Jepoy] Don't touch me!
-Madrigal--
-[Jepoy growls]
-Don't touch me.
-Fine!
If you don't need my help…
Well, let's take a good look around.
There's no one else here to help you.
I think you just have to accept the fact…
that I'm all you've got.
Why don't you wrap that head
of yours around this thought?
[scoffs]
You…
have got…
-me.
-[Jepoy scoffs]
You know what?
You're so full of yourself.
I don't need your help.
And I will never ask for your help.
Got that?
-No.
-Leave me alone.
-I can take care of myself.
-I don't understand.
I don't understand
what you're talking about.
All I can remember…
is that the last time…
we had a chance to hang out,
you were willing to throw away
all you had with Anna…
just to have one last taste of me.
Do you remember?
Watch your mouth.
Whether you admit it or not
and no matter how many times
you tell me that you love Anna,
your blood craves for me.
You want me…
and you need me.
I have everything you need, Madrigal.
I have power.
I have even more money now.
I can take care of you.
Everything you want…
I have.
And I'm willing to give it to you.
[Helena] You can't even
finish off your opponent!
You couldn't kill up front.
Because I don't get my hands dirty, Mama.
[Helena] If you want to
succeed in business,
you need to be hands-on.
But don't worry.
Pretty soon, you're going to get
the killer instinct like your son.
But I do have a killer instinct, Mama.
So prove it.
[laughs viciously]
I think I'll be needing you…
sooner than later.
[laughs viciously]
I love it!
Let me take care of you.
I don't love you.
[scorns]
[scoffs] Aren't you tired of saying that?
[sighs heavily]
I'm tired of hearing it.
If you really want to help Lily Cruz,
listen carefully, Madrigal.
I inherited…
one of the Big Four's armies.
Plus…
I inherited…
fake Jaguar's men.
Right?
I can tell them to help you
if I wanted to.
[Natalie] I could also ask them
to beat the living crap out of you
when you're being dumb.
Stop being so foolish, Madrigal.
I can give you everything you need.
I want to give you everything.
I can do…
whatever it is you want me to do.
And they'll listen.
Because I
am
their
queen.
Emilia. How are you?
To what do I owe this pleasure, Raul?
Of course, I missed you.
I missed being with you and your family.
I missed Mama and Papa.
So, do you mind if I come along?
Oh my gosh, Raul.
You're trying to sweet talk me
because you want something from me.
What are you talking about, Emilia?
You found out that your
son, Diego, is missing.
Now you think my family
has something to do with it.
That's why you're trying to sweet talk me.
Wait.
What do you mean Diego's missing?
What does Diego have to do with this?
First, Lily goes missing. Now, Diego too?
What are you talking about?
-Goodbye, Raul.
-Hold on, we're not yet done.
-Ow! Let me go!
-What have you done to Diego?
Wait!
Everyone has their secrets, Raul.
Deal with it.
-Get back here, Emilia!
-Let's go!
Emilia!
Emilia! I'll find out what you're hiding!
Emilia, we aren't done yet!
[panting]
[ragged breathing]
What are you doing?!
I'm looking for the gun
that will kill you!
You're out of your mind!
Instead of yapping,
why don't you look for the gun,
so you can save Lily?
We'll just serve her food.
Hand it to her.
[man] Here, eat that.
Eat up.
How am I supposed to eat this?
We won't give you utensils.
[man] We can't take any chances.
You're tougher than Catwoman,
and you're more slippery than an eel.
You might use the utensils to kill us.
So, just eat with your hands!
Well, I'm not a superhero.
So, I won't be able to do that to you.
You read too many comics.
I'm already on death row,
and this is the food you give me?!
Still pretty smug, aren't you?
You think you're on death row?
Isn't it obvious?
Eat up!
[sinister music playing]
[groans]
-[Lily groans]
-What is it this time?
-I don't feel so good.
-[man scoffs]
I don't know if this food's gone bad…
or if it's just really bad.
I need to use the bathroom.
Damn it.
Did you hear me?
I said I need to use the bathroom!
Do you want me to go right here?!
Fine!
Untie her.
[man] Get her plate too.
Don't try anything funny.
Don't tell me you're still
going to use those.
Fine.
Help her.
Don't try anything funny.
-Hurry.
-Don't touch me!
You know, I don't need any weapons.
I can kill you if I want.
We're here.
-Let go!
-I said we're here!
There's your restroom!
You have ten minutes.
We can help you if you want.
Go.
Stop it!
Cut it out, perverts!
I can do it myself.
[man] Well, go in.
You've got ten minutes.
[tense music playing]
[tense music continues playing]
You want to touch it?
Go ahead. It's okay.
Come on.
[suspenseful music playing]
Hey! [knocking on door]
Five minutes left.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Camia screams]
[grunts]
[man howls in pain]
[howling in pain]
She got away!
Get her!
[screaming] Looking for this?!
It's right here.
Are you ready to die?!
Huh?!
[tense music playing]
You win.
Shoot.
Kill me.
Then kill Camia next.
And you and Lily can flee.
Shoot me.
Come on. Shoot me!
[in low voice] Pull the trigger.
Kill me now! Come on!
What are you waiting for?!
Pull the trigger! Come on!
Come on!
Now!
Do it! Do it!
Shoot him! Come on, Diego!
Shoot!
Wait, Mama.
Don't tell me you'll let Lily Cruz live?
That's unacceptable!
She's the root of our misery.
And she's the reason
why you came back for me!
We'll exact revenge on her, right?
Then why are you just
standing there, Mama?
And making her come out
alive in this hell?
No, no, no, Grandma.
Don't listen to her.
-Oh, come on, Arnaldo!
-Let Diego win this round.
[scoffs] You're just saying that
because you still have
feelings for Lily Cruz!
That's why you want Diego
to shoot Damian, so that Lily can--
-You know damn well that's not the reason!
-Enough!
This is a game.
And it isn't over yet.
I promise you, when this is all over,
everything will go back to the
way it should always be.
So, carry on.
Your time's up!
[man] Hey!
Come out!
One!
I said come out!
Shoot me.
Shoot me!
[man screams]
[man 2] Boss!
Go after Camia Cruz! Hurry!
Now!
-Hurry up!
-No.
Took you long enough in there.
-You're so slow!
-Hey!
Get moving!
-Move it!
-Don't push me!
Sit down!
[man] What's this?
You sneaky rat!
Trying to pull something off, huh?
Put this on the record!
My pencil's gone!
It's missing?
Borrow mine!
[grunts]
[gunshot]
[tense music playing]
Where is she? Hey, wake up!
Wake up!
Come on! We need to find her! Get up!
Get up!
Move it!
[Helena] It's crunch time!
So, you have to kill
whoever you have to kill…
in order to survive!
What?
What?! Camia got away?!
[Emilia] What?!
[suspenseful music playing]
Lily Cruz is getting away!
-[Helena growls]
-[Emilia screams]
Lily?
Where are you going?!
You witch!
I won't let you escape again!
Mama, enough!
-Enough, Mama!
-Helena!
-How did this happen?!
[Julio] Helena, relax!
Hold your horses!
Here comes the savior!
[laughs viciously]
How can you still laugh?!
[Helena] Can't you see that Lily
Cruz is getting away?!
That is why I will always be
better than you are, my dear.
[Julio] Now, relax!
Take a deep breath.
Inhale, exhale.
Do the same.
And watch what happens.
Watch as I command Lily Cruz…
to lay down!
[electric zaps]
[laughing viciously]
See? Told you!
She follows! She's very good!
One more time!
-[electric zaps]
-[Lily gasps]
[Ardientes laughing viciously]
[Emilia] This is fantastic, Papa!
I told you I had everything under control.
[Emilia laughs viciously]
-Can you do it again?
-Do it again?
By the request of my grandson…
Lie down! [laughs]
-[laughing viciously]
-[electric zaps]
[Julio] Stay! [laughs viciously]
-[laughing viciously]
-[electric zaps]
[electric zaps]
-[laughing viciously]
-[electric zaps]
[Julio] Sit! [laughs viciously]
-[laughing viciously]
-[electric zaps]
[inaudible]
[electric zapping]
[Fernan] We saw some
trucks pass by earlier.
It looked like they were
carrying the Ardientes' men.
Where were they headed?
I think they were heading
to the heart of the forest.
Mister Fernan, everyone…
We have no one else
to rely on, but each other.
If anyone has doubts
about rescuing Auntie Camia and Lily,
you can stay behind.
-We're going.
-We're going with you.
-Very well, let's go.
-Let's go.
-Let's go, everyone!
Hold on, Anna.
Are you sure about this?
This could be dangerous!
Marlon, if I don't do this then who will?
I knew it.
Jepoy influenced you to do this.
Jepoy has nothing to do with this!
This is for Lily and Auntie Camia.
Will you listen to yourself, Marlon?
ANNA AND THE MEMBERS
OF THE COOPERATIVE
ARE LOOKING FOR LILY.
We still need more information.
We can't just move without a plan.
If you don't want to help,
then stay here!
[Anna] Come on.
[Julio] You know…
I like my steak rare.
I mean, very rare.
Because it…
basically reminds me
of how cruel the animal…
-was handled…
-[Helena laughs]
…before it was served.
Well…
it makes a lot of difference.
You're right.
But, then again,
I would be a lot happier
if we were devouring Lily Cruz
and her mother's flesh instead.
My dear…
I will never let you down.
You know what?
That electronic dog
collar? That was brilliant!
But then, you were a little too sadistic.
You allowed me to panic
before you pushed that button!
Of course!
Where's the fun in it?
A little suspense won't hurt, right?
And, you must admit…
my men moved fast…
fast enough to kill Camia's
fantasy of escaping.
You know what?
As much as I hate you
to the very core of my being,
Ouch!
I must say…
you are…
the perfect partner.
[laughs]
No, my dear.
You are…
my…
perfect partner.
Let me help you.
Let's go kill our babies!
Damn, Helena!
What am I doing here?!
Will you let me out of here?!
Hey!
-[slams door]
-I said, let me out of here!
[Camia on video recording] You monsters!
What are you going to do to me?!
Mom!
[Camia on video recording] You monsters!
[Camia] You monsters!
Where's my daughter?!
You bastards! What are you
doing to my mother?!
Mom!
[Camia on video recording] You monsters!
[Camia wails]
[Camia] Let Lily go!
You bastards!
[sobbing] You monsters!
Lily!
Mom!
[Julio] We'll drive her insane,
as she did my grandson.
Not so tough now, are we?
Why don't you come closer?
[grunting]
[Diego] Listen to me.
We don't have to kill each other.
We can save Auntie Camia and Lily
if you cooperate with me.
We're going to turn the tables on them.
[gunshot]
[Lily] Show yourselves!
Come out and face me!
Don't be cowards!
Come and get me, Ardientes!
Where's my mother?!
-[gunshots]
-[Lily screams]
[theme music playing]